Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Evan Wolfson Files, 1948-2009; Series I; 20.5; (44 boxes)
  - Early marriage organizing files, 1948-2009
    - Freedom to Marry Coalition steering committee
      - 1996 March 4, 1996 February 15-March 4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - 1996 April 19, 1996 March 19-April 19 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - 1996 June 3, 1996 May 20-June 3 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - 1996 June 15 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - 1996 October 7, 1996 July 17-October 7 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - 1997 January 13, 1997-01-05 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - 1997 February 21, 1997 February 14-March 11 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - 1997 April 7, 1997 April 1-3 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - 1997 May 12, 1997 May 5-13 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - 1997 June 30, 1997 May 13-July 10 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - 1997 September 5, 1997 August 27-September 5 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - 1997 November 10, 1997 November 4-28 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - 1998 January 12, 1997 December 19-1998 January 15 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - 1998 February 9, 1998 February 5 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - 1998 March 9, 1998 March 4-9 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - 1998 April 6, 1998 March 4-1998 March 30 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - 1998 July 13, 1998 July 7-16 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - 1998 September 1, 1998 August 25-September 1 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Freedom to Marry steering committee
      - 1996 December 9, 1996 November 11-December 9 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - 1998 October 5, 1998 September 29-October 5 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - 1999 January 11, 1998 December 8-1999 January 11 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - 1999 April 19, 1999 April 12-19 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - 1999 June 14 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Full faith and credit - the lawyers clause of the Constitution, 1945 January (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Gay, Lesbian, Straight Education Network, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Goodridge v. Department of Public Health (Massachusetts 2001), 2001-2003 (Box 13, Folder 31, Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Groups partners task force, 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hawaii marriage decision paper and letters (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Historical materials (marriage project), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Home state marriage civil litigation notes (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - International
      - Canada, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6-8, Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Canada M v. H decision (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
      - Canada marriage litigation (Box 15, Folder 4-6)
      - Canada same-sex (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Canada, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - China/Asia, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Colombia, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Denmark, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - General, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - International Lesbian and Gay Law Association (ILGLA) w/ William Institute Conference, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Ireland (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
      - Ireland, 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Israel, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Japan, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Japan - occur case (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - South Africa, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - South America (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Sweden (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - United Kingdom (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Intra-community shorts, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Jones v. Hallahan, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Law review journals, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Legal case news clippings, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Legal issues divorce/dissolutions, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Legal issues: Incest, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Legal issues polygamy, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Legal issues transsexuals, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Legal New York City Bar Association report, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Legal: right to marry - nepotism (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "Let no one set asunder" paper and commentary by Rilea Brilmayer, 1994 November 7 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "Let no one set asunder" paper drafts and outlines, 1995 October (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "Let no one set asunder" paper drafts and outlines, 1995 October; 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Lewis v. Harris New Jersey/main case, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mailing lists, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Massachussetts, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Matter of Cooper (2d Dept. 1992) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - McConnell v. Anderson (8th Cir. 1971) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Mellman poll on DOMA [Defense of Marriage Act], 1996 June 5 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Miller v. Supreme court (CA), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - M.T. v. J.T. New Jersey (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - National collaborative meeting, 2004 June 9 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey main case, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Next wave: constitutional rights: privileges and immunities clauses (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Opposition
      - 2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - American Center for Law and Justice (ACLJ), 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Anti-marriage campaign (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Family research (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Hawaii, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Lou Sheldon - degendering, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Mailings/materials from religious political extremists (RPEs), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Mormons, 1995-2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - National campaign to protect marriage, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Op-eds letters to the editor, etc, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Religious political extremists (RPE), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Religious political extremists attack on LAMBDA, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Rex Lee, Lynn Wardle, etc, 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - The Rutherford Institute, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Scholarship (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Vermont (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Outreach
      - 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Marriage meeting, 2003 September 8 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Freedom to Marry Day, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - National Freedom to Marry Day, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - National Freedom to Marry Day 1999: editorials (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - New York City marriage meeting, 2003 July 21 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Youth, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Partners, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Perez v. Lippold California (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Polling
      - California CA 2000 prop 22: focus group, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - General, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
      - General, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Hawaii constitutional amendment, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Hawaii Equal Rights Marriage Project (confidential), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Human Rights Campaign (HRC), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Human Rights Campaign (HRC), 1996 November (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Human Rights Campaign (HRC), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - International (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Interracial (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Iowa, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Lesbian/Gay community (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Michigan, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - New Hampshire, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Newsweek, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Newsweek, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - NGLTF: National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1998 May (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - New York Marriage, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Oregon, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Parenting, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Washington (Good), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Time, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Vermont (Right Wing), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Vermont, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Vermont Freedom to Marry task force (good), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Wall Street Journal/NBC, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Youth, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - 1998 New York (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - 1999 general (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - 1999: NYS confidential (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - 2000 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - 2001 Youth (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - 1996 - Harris (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - 1997 California Field Poll (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - 1997 college (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - 1997 -general (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - 1997 Washington (Bad) (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Press - stories people of color, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Press - stories religious, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Resolutions (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Resolutions: campus outreach (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Resolution: drafts (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Resolution: groups to solicit (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Same-sex marriage and choice-of-law by Barbara Cox, annotated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Singer v. Hara, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Steering committee
      - Articles about FMC (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - General - notes (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - Goals/message/languages subcommittee (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - List (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - Mid-year meeting, 2005 March 4-5 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - October 1995 announcement, 1995 October (Box 22, Folder 45)
      - Public relations working group, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - Timeline/strategy subcommittee (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - 1995 February 22 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - 1995 April 18 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - 1995 June 13 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - 1995 July 24 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - 1995 September 11 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Summit follow-up, 1994 December 9 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Summit 10/28/94, 1994 October 28 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Supporters
      - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1996-2008 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - American psychoanalytic association, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - And Justice for All, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Bar associations, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Celebrities contacts (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Celebrities correspondence, 1991-2003 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Celebrities general supporters, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Celebrities material (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Celebrities resolution signatories list, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Gay and Lesbian Parents Coalition International (GCPCI), parent groups (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - GLBTQ Legal Advocates and Defenders (GLAD), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Human Rights Campaign: criticism, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Human Rights Campaign: fundraising/events (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Human Rights Campaign: Hawaii/POC, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Human Rights Campaign: marriage, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Human Rights Campaign: meetings/notes, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Human Rights Campaign: (MMOW) Millennium March on Washington DC, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Human Rights Campaign: organizing, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Human Rights Campaign: postings/correspondence, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Human Rights Campaign: Press, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Human Rights Campaign: publications: general, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Human Rights Campaign: publications: marriage (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Japanese-American Citizens League (JACL), 1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Lesbian and Gay Immigration Rights Task Force (LGIRTF), 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Libertarian party, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Log cabin republicans, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Marriage equality, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Inc. Fund, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - National Association of Social Workers (NASW), 1996 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - National Organization for Women, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - National LGBT Task Force (NGLTF), 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - No, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - National Organization for Women (NOW), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Parenting, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - People for the American Way, 1996-2004 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - People of color groups, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Religious: coalition, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Religious groups: Buddhism, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Religious groups: Catholic, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Religious groups: Christians, 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Religious groups: Christian, Ecumenical Catholic (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Religious groups: Christians Episcopalian, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Religious groups: Christian evangelical anglican church in America, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Religious groups, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Religious groups: Christians: Metropolitan Community Churches, 1995-1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Religious groups: Christians: Methodist, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Religious groups: Christians: Methodists: activism, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Religious groups: Christians: Presbyterians, 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Religious groups: Christians: Quakers, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Religious groups: Christians: United Church of Christ, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Religious groups: Christians: United Church of Christ: ERCL startup packet (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Religious groups: Christians: Unitarians, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Religious groups: Judaism, 1995-2002 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Religious groups: Lambda organizing, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Religious groups: other, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Religious groups: Unitarian Universalist, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Timeline/strategy subcommittee, 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Transexuals cases, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Transsexual: cases: Littleton v. Prange, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Trial CT news, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Work draft of a paper, 1996 March 26 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Varnum v. Brien marriage case - Iowa Supreme Court, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Victories and losses notes, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Freedom to Marry files, 2001-2008
    - AL-Action alert-ASAP email, 2005 February 16 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Administrative assistant (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Administrative assistant applications, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Administrative assistant applicatons, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Administrative assistant applications (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
    - Administrative assistant hiring emails, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Administrative assistant question emails, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Administrative assistant 2IT applications, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Administrative assistant 2 applications, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Barbara Bailey interview email, 2001 May 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Bryce Cutler interview notes email, 2001 June 6 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Calendar FW: Rhode Island page, 2005 February 10 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Candidate's advisory on how to support marriage equality (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Changes to Wisconsin calendar email, 2005 February 10 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Development, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Equal rights Colorado action alert SB05-140 on liming legal implications of marriage, 2005 February 10 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Freedom to Marry week event correspondence, 2005 January 3 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Loving, 2007 June 7 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Pamphlet folder (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Print mats in progress (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Program director, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Samiya Bashir - mail (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Super-DOMA is dead email, 2005 February 16 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Tax time campaign, 2007 April 4 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Week report (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 2004 campaign seven conversations in seven days (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 2008 election (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Lambda Legal files, 1958-2001
    - Adoption and foster care (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Civil rights issues activism demonstration (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Civil rights issues: economic effects of discrimination (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Bills of Attainder (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Board reports
      - 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - 1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - 1992-1998 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Calhart/other admin (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Constitutional rights equal protection articles (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional rights equal protection gender discrimination (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Constitutional rights - equal protection standard of review, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Constitutional rights - equal protection "suspect class" heightened scrutiny (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Constitutional rights privacy Richards article 30, Hastings, New Jersey (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Constitutional rights privacy - State priv. amendments (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Constitutional rights - privileges and immunities, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Exempt organization certification (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Exempt organization certification (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Family relationships - adoption Hope I (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Family relationships marriage pre-nuptial agreements (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Family relationships parenting Walsh v. Walsh (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Gay parenting articles (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - The Lambda update, 1958-1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Lambda newsletter archives, 1976-1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Lambda personnel file (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Legal defense and education fund (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Meeting memorandums and notes, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Military don't ask don't tell (DADA), 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Multi-cultural committee inter-office memo, 1991 October 12 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Multi-cultural committee research (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Miss Saigon (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Miss Saigon coalition (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Miss Saigon coalition meeting, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon Lambra org in-house stuff (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon lyrics, 1991 April (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Miss Saigon - anti-Miss Saigon materials, 1991 April (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Miss Saigon - news clippings (Lambda + Miss Saigon), 1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Miss Saigon - news clippings (general), 1991 April (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Miss Saigon protest memos, 1991 April (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Miss Saigon subcommittee stuff (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Multi-cultural articles - board training, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Parenting - donor issues surrogacy, 1988-1993 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Parenting groups/resources (Box 31, Folder 15-16)
    - Saigon board packets, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Saigon disk, 1 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Saigon subcommittee letters in response to appeals (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Salary, 1989-1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Sodomy - Louisiana v. Boxley lambda amicus brief, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - States recognition of same-sex marriages performed in other states, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Stottard/Ettelbrook years (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Supreme court Ruth Ginsberg nomination (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Supreme court Souter nomination, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Supreme court of the United States, 1989-1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, Judge Clarence, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - To be filed research and memos (Box 32, Folder 10-11)
    - Vermont civil unions organizing (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Year in review, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Year in review, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Year in review, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Year in review, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Press clippings, 1989-2005
    - 1989 July-December (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 1990 January-June (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 1990 July-December (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 1991 January-June (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 1991 July-December (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Harvard Journal of Law and Public Policy volume 14 number 1, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - 1992 January-June (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 1992 July-December (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - 1993 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - 1994 January-June (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 1994 July-December (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Review of Law and Social Change numbers, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 1995 July-December (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 1995 July-December (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 1996 January-June (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - 1996 July-December (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - CBS this morning, 1996 December 4 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 1996 December (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - The Right to Marry: Allerdice high school graduate is leading the way in the battle to win legal recognition for same-sex marriage, 1997 March 11 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Out Magazine gay celebrities, 2001 January (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - From Boy Scouts to marriage: engaging non-gay America to win full equality for all, 2001 January-February (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Why the Boy Scouts case went down, 2001 January-February (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Wolfson leaving Lambda articles, 2001 March (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - The Journal: Temple considers ending ties to scouts, 2001 April 23 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - The Legal Intelligeneer people in the news, 2001 April 26 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Making History: Gay community celebrates world's first same-sex marriage, 2001 April 27 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Bay Times: National bits and pieces, 2001 May 3 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Debate simmers over Scouts' ban, 2001 June 15 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - New York Times: Reviews and news, 2001 June 19 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - The New York Times: The Boy Scout amendment, 2001 June 20 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - In strength, in honor, involved, 2002 June 22 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - The Washington Blade, 2001 June 22 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Lesbian Gay New York (LGNY) city, 2001 July 19 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Lesbian Gay New York (LGNY) Latino (Spanish), 2001 August 2 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - All together now, 2001 September 11 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Marriage redefined, 2002 August 25 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Gay city news, 2003 March 7-13 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - The Advocate: Marriage on his mind, 2003 June 23 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - The Flipside same sex debate CNN transcript, 2003 July 14 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - The Threat to marriage from the courts, 2003 July 29 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Gay city news, 2003 July 21-31 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Progress at last? Equal rights is for gay, lesbian, bisexual and transgender people, 2003 August 2 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Colorful witnesses to testify on gay marriage, 2003 September 5 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - The CQ Researcher: gay marriage, 2003 September 5 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - New York Blade: GOP no-shows may hurt 'DOMA' hearings, 2003 September 12 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Gay City News editorial, 2003 September 19-25 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Canada dodges anti-gay bullets, 2003 September 19-25 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - The Advocate Report: Arizona aisle appeal, 2003 September 30 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Non-discrimination in civil marriage: perspectives from international human rights laws and practice, 2003 September (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Gay city news, 2003 October 2-3 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - The New York Sun: Out and about, 2003 October 14 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Human Rights Campaign full page ad, 2003 October 17 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - New York Blade: New York Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) celebrates 30 years, 2003 October 17 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Gay city news, 2003 November 20-26 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Massachusetts court rules 'yes' on gay marriage, 2003 November 21 (Box 37, Folder 37)